{
    "id": "22cd4b72229e4821922a23d5b0a4bed7",
    "title": "Conjunctions And Linkers Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I don't know ...................................... I would get the job.",
            "description": "If or whether can introduce an indirect question.",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "weather",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c7056780011d4fcab469651dd49fc6d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "They cancelled the match .............................. bad weather.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because of",
                "on account of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e1afa5c9c8c044b4b343d426b9b0230c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He still drives that old car ............................... he has enough money to buy a new car.",
            "description": "Either though or even though is possible here. Even though is more emphatic than though.",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "even if",
                "even though"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ac8334f97a274b4ab97aaff9a8dfa7de"
        },
        {
            "question": "I learned Spanish ............................... be able to find a job during my stay in Spain.",
            "description": "Both expressions indicate purpose.",
            "answers": [
                "in order to",
                "so as to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d92e1536665f4bc88536abd3ec0b83fd"
        },
        {
            "question": "It seems .................................... somebody had opened the door.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as if",
                "as though",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "188729c417404610b6ef5c51504691e3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Break the glass ................................. fire.",
            "description": "If is used before a clause. In case of and in the event of are used before a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "in case of",
                "in the event of",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "68e33082b68144ac9538d7ab1160229b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ordered food online ................................. I didn't have enough time to cook.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "because",
                "though",
                "Either as or because"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "ae54cdc06c944a4abc196dc85113ed59"
        },
        {
            "question": "It rained several times ................................ the night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "during",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a83dc77f191e4fb59abec70dac84e572"
        },
        {
            "question": "We can't leave ............................... he returns.",
            "description": "Till and until mean the same till is more common in an informal style. ",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "till",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "19d00dbf736d493ab4277d35cd105a56"
        },
        {
            "question": "They couldn't save her .............................. their best efforts.",
            "description": "Either despite or in spite of is possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "despite",
                "in spite of",
                "inspite of",
                "despite of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c95a23d2046b42d98fbf4ef5c503dbe7"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… hard you may try, you will not finish that task.",
            "description": "However hard means the same as it doesn't matter how hard.",
            "answers": [
                "No matter",
                "However",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3cc1f9bb9962414088ac3fff529b7dd5"
        },
        {
            "question": "She looked pale ……………………………. she had seen a ghost.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as if",
                "as though",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "36fcef1c8e634862be4b8efc017fc6fe"
        }
    ]
}